Guide to the Records of the American Institute of the City of New York for the Encouragement of Science and Invention 1808-1983 (bulk, 1828-1940) MS 17
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Annual Fair Years, 1808-1930
  - Subseries 2: Administrative, 1808-1930
    - "Treasurer's Authority to Pay Bills, 1851-1879" (2 of 2), 1869-1879 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 1)
    - "Applications for Membership of the American Institute, 1852" (Offsite-box 86, Folder 2)
    - "Reports and Papers, 1852", 1851-1852 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 3)
    - "Vouchers from April 1852 to April 1853", 1852-1853 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 4)
    - "Applications for Membership of the American Institute 1853" (Offsite-box 86, Folder 5)
    - Cash Annual Elections, 1853-1872 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 6)
    - "Reports and Papers, 1853" (Offsite-box 86, Folder 7)
    - "Constitution and Members of the Home League of the State of New York", 1853 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 8)
    - "List of Members of the French National Institute", 1853 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 9)
    - "Vouchers from April 1853 to April 1854", 1853-1854 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 1)
    - "Applications for Membership, 1854" (Offsite-box 87, Folder 2)
    - "Reports and Papers, 1854" (Offsite-box 87, Folder 3)
    - "Vouchers from April 1854 to April 1855", 1853-1855 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 4)
    - "Applications for Membership, 1855", 1854-1855 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 5)
    - "Reports and Papers - 1855" (Offsite-box 87, Folder 6)
    - Old Checks, 1855 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 7)
    - "Vouchers from April 1855 to April 1856", 1855-1856 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 8)
    - "Members Admitting - Nov. 6, 1856" (Offsite-box 88, Folder 1)
    - Photographs - Made by Chas. Wagner Hull of the American Institute (Photograph and Print) [Removed to Visual Materials Box], [1856] (Offsite-box 88, Folder 2)
    - "Reports and Papers - 1856" (Offsite-box 88, Folder 3)
    - "Vouchers from May 1, 1856 - April 30, 1857", 1856-1857 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 4)
    - "Applications for Membership - 1857", 1856-1858 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 5)
    - Reports - 1857 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 6)
    - "Reports and Papers, 1857" (Offsite-box 88, Folder 7)
    - Payrolls and Bills, 1857-1858 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 8)
    - "Vouchers from May 1, 1857 to Jan 1, 1858", 1856-1858 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 9)
    - Contracts and Agreements, 1857-1858 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 10)
    - "Applications for Membership 1858" (Offsite-box 88, Folder 11)
    - "Reports and Papers 1858" (Offsite-box 89, Folder 1)
    - "Original Lease of Crystal Palace, 1858" (Offsite-box 89, Folder 2)
    - "Vouchers from Feb. 1, 1858 to Jan. 1, 1859", 1858-1859 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 3)
    - "Applications for Membership 1859" (Offsite-box 89, Folder 4)
    - "Correspondence of John Stuart and William Leonard", 1859-1865 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 5)
    - "Letters 1859", 1859-1860 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 6)
    - "Reports and Papers 1859" (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 89, Folder 7)
    - "Reports and Papers 1859" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 89, Folder 8)
    - "Reports of the Finance Committee, American Institute, 1859 to 1874" (1 of 2), 1868-1875 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 9)
    - "Reports of the Finance Committee, American Institute, 1859 to 1874" (2 of 2), 1868-1875 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 1)
    - "Vouchers from Feb 1st, 1859 - Feb 1st, 1860", 1857-1860 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 2)
    - "Leases, Cooper Union to American Institute, 1859 to 1878, 1879 to 1884", 1859, 1866-1884 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 3)
    - "Applications for Membership, 1860" (Offsite-box 90, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and Notes, 1860 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 5)
    - "Life Members and Annual Members, American Institute, 1860 (1 of 2), 1855-1856 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 6)
    - "Life Members and Annual Members, American Institute, 1860" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 90, Folder 7)
    - "Reports and Papers - 1860" (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 90, Folder 8)
    - "Reports and Papers, 1860" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 90, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1860-1863 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1860-1863 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 2)
    - "Vouchers from Feb. 1, 1860 to Jan. 31, 1861" (1 of 2), 1859-1861 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 3)
    - "Vouchers from Feb. 1, 1860 to Jan. 31, 1861" (2 of 2), 1859-1861 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 4)
    - "Report on Salt", 1860-1862 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 5)
    - "Vouchers, Feb. 1st, 1861 - Jan. 31, 1862", 1860-1861 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 6)
    - "Applications for Membership, 1861", 1860-1861 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 7)
    - "Reports and Papers, 1861" (Offsite-box 91, Folder 8)
    - Reports and Papers, 1861, 1860-1861 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 9)
    - "Election Expenses 1861, '62, '63, '64 and '65", 1861-1866 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 10)
    - Poll List of the American Institute, 1861-1869, 1871 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 1)
    - "Propositions for Membership, 1862" (Offsite-box 92, Folder 2)
    - "Reports and Papers, 1862" (Offsite-box 92, Folder 3)
    - "Reports, Essays, 1862" (Offsite-box 92, Folder 4)
    - "Vouchers, Feb. 1st, 1862 - Jan. 31st, 1863", 1861-1863 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 5)
    - "Propositions for Membership, 1863" (Offsite-box 92, Folder 6)
    - "1863" Reports and Papers (Offsite-box 92, Folder 7)
    - "Vouchers from Feb. 1, 1863 to Jan. 31, 1864", 1862-1863 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 8)
    - "Propositions for Membership, 1864" (Offsite-box 92, Folder 9)
    - "Letters, 1864" (Offsite-box 92, Folder 10)
    - "Reports and Papers -- American Institute, 1864", 1863-1864 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 11)
    - Horticultural Association of the American Institute, 1864 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 12)
    - "Rough Minutes, Horticultural Assn. of the American Institute, 1864 '65", 1864-1865 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 1)
    - "Vouchers from Feb. 1, 1864 to Jan. 31, 1865 -- American Institute", 1863-1865 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 2)
    - "Propositions for Membership, 1865" (Offsite-box 93, Folder 3)
    - "Reports and Papers -- American Institute, 1865" (Offsite-box 93, Folder 4)
    - "Vouchers from Feb. 1, 1865 to Jan. 31, 1866" (Offsite-box 93, Folder 5)
    - "Propositions for Membership, 1866", 1865-1866 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 6)
    - "Reports and Papers -- American Institute, 1866" (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 93, Folder 7)
    - "Reports and Papers -- American Institute, 1866" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 94, Folder 1)
    - "Vouchers -- American Institute, 1866" (Offsite-box 94, Folder 2)
    - "Propositions for Membership, 1867" (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 94, Folder 3)
    - "Propositions for Membership, 1867" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 94, Folder 4)
    - "Reports and Papers -- American Institute, 1867" (Offsite-box 94, Folder 5)
    - "Rough Minutes -- Board of Managers, 1867" (Offsite-box 94, Folder 6)
    - "Vouchers -- American Institute, 1867" (Offsite-box 94, Folder 7)
    - "Propositions for Membership, 1868", 1867-1868 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 1)
    - "L. Carr Wood Papers, 1868" (Offsite-box 95, Folder 2)
    - "Reports and Papers -- American Institute, 1868" (Offsite-box 95, Folder 3)
    - "Reports of the Clerk -- Members in arrears for dues, 1868, '69 '70' and '71", 1867-1872 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 4)
    - "Vouchers, 1868" (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 95, Folder 5)
    - "Vouchers, 1868" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 95, Folder 6)
    - "1st Course, Scientific Lectures, 1868 '69 -- Vouchers", 1868-1869 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 7)
    - "Propositions for Membership, 1869" (1 of 2), 1868-1869 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 8)
    - "Propositions for Membership, 1869" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 96, Folder 1)
    - "Reports and Papers, 1869" (Offsite-box 96, Folder 2)
    - "Papers in Relation to Empire City Skating Rink, 1869", 1869-1871 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 3)
    - "Vouchers -- American Institute, 1869" (Offsite-box 96, Folder 4)
    - "2nd Course, Scientific Lectures, 1879 '70 -- Vouchers", 1869-1870 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 5)
    - "Propositions for Membership, 1870" (Offsite-box 96, Folder 6)
    - "Reports and Papers, American Institute, 1870" (Offsite-box 96, Folder 7)
    - Reports and Papers, American Institute, 1870 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 8)
    - "Relating to the Trial of Phleger Boiler -- B -- 1870" (Offsite-box 96, Folder 9)
    - Poll Lists, American Institute, 1870-1879, 1882-1883 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 10)
    - Leases/Insurance, 1870-1871 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 1)
    - "Vouchers American Institute, 1870" (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 97, Folder 2)
    - "Vouchers American Institute, 1870" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 97, Folder 3)
    - "3d Course Scientific Lectures 1870 '71 -- Vouchers", 1870-1871 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 4)
    - "Petty Cash Bills 1870 to 1874" (1 of 2), 1870-1872 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 5)
    - "Petty Cash Bills -- 1870 to 1874" (2 of 2), 1873-1874 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 6)
    - "Trustee Papers (1)", 1870-1871 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 7)
    - "Propositions for Membership. 1871." (1 of 2), 1870-1871 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 8)
    - "Propositions for Membership. 1871." (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 97, Folder 9)
    - Appendix - Life Members of American Institute, [1871] (Offsite-box 97, Folder 10)
    - Membership Materials and Resignations, 1871-1879 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 1)
    - Reports and Papers, 1871 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 2)
    - "Trustee Papers (2)", 1871-1872 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 3)
    - "Maxim Eagle Gas Machine Co. Papers", 1871-1872 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 4)
    - Leases/Contracts, 1871 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 5)
    - "Vouchers American Institute 1871" (1 of 2), 1870-1871 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 6)
    - "Vouchers American Institute 1871" (2 of 2), 1869-1872 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 7)
    - "4th Course Scientific Lectures 1871 '72 Vouchers", 1871-1872 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 8)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1872" (1 of 2), 1871-1872 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 9)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1872" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 98, Folder 10)
    - "Resignation and Declinations 1872", 1872-1873 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 11)
    - "Memorandums and Odd Papers -- Whitman Estate", 1872-1878 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 12)
    - Reports and Papers, 1872 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 13)
    - Photographic Section, 1872 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 14)
    - "Rough Minutes -- Farmers Club -- Oct. 22 1872 to July 1, 1873" (1 of 2), 1872-1873 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 15)
    - "Rough Minutes -- Farmers Club -- Oct. 22 1872 to July 1, 1873" (2 of 2), 1871-1873 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 1)
    - Leases/Contracts/Insurance, 1872 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 2)
    - "Vouchers 1872" (1 of 2), 1871-1873 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 3)
    - "Vouchers 1872" (2 of 2), 1871-1873 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 4)
    - "5th Course, Scientific Lectures 1872 '73, Vouchers", 1873 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 5)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1873", 1872 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 6)
    - "Correspondence Whitmore Est. Excepting Letters of Mrs. Whitmore 1873", 1873; N.D. (Offsite-box 99, Folder 7)
    - "Correspondence with Mrs. Whitmore 1873, 1874, 1875, 1876", 1874-1876 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 8)
    - Legal Papers of Connecticut Trust 1873", 1872-1874 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 9)
    - "List of Bonds/Stocks and Memorandums - therewith 1873", 1873; 1876 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 10)
    - "Old Papers from Superintendent's Office - Blanks used at Exhibitions, 1873 to 1878. Papers relating to Charter Matters at Albany" (1 of 2), 1874-1875 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 11)
    - "Old Papers from Superintendent's Office - Blanks used at Exhibitions, 1873 to 1878. Papers relating to Charter Matters at Albany" (2 of 2), 1874-1878 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 12)
    - Reports and Papers - The American Institute, 1873 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 13)
    - "Reports Photographical Section 1873" (Offsite-box 99, Folder 14)
    - "Receipts Previous to Settlement of Estate in Connecticut July 1, 1873", 1872-1873 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 1)
    - Vouchers "1873" (Offsite-box 100, Folder 2)
    - "Vouchers. American Institute. 1873" (1 of 2), 1873-1874 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 3)
    - "Vouchers. American Institute. 1873" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 100, Folder 4)
    - Vouchers, 1873-1878 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 5)
    - "Returns of the Inspectors of the Annual Elections, American Institute 1873, 78-79, 1900-1919" (1 of 3), 1873, 1878-1890 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 6)
    - "Returns of the Inspectors of the Annual Elections, American Institute 1873, 78-79, 1900-1919" (2 of 3), 1891-1905 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 7)
    - "Returns of the Inspectors of the Annual Elections, American Institute 1873, 78-79, 1900-1919" (3 of 3), 1906-1919 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 8)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1874", 1873-1874 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 1)
    - "1874" [Board of Directors], 1873-1874 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 2)
    - "Annual Statements to Heirs, to July 1, 1874 [to July] 1, 1875 -- for Copies of all Later Statements and c see Letter Book", 1874-1875 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 3)
    - "Legal Papers and Letter of W.J. Hoppin 1874; Correspondence Whitmore Estate Excepting Letters of Mrs. Whitmore 1874", 1873-1876 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 4)
    - "Report of Committee to Test the Howard Boilers Dec. 14, 1874" (Offsite-box 101, Folder 5)
    - "Reports and Papers American Institute 1874" (Offsite-box 101, Folder 6)
    - "Reports Photographical Section 1874" (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 101, Folder 7)
    - "Reports Photographical Section 1874" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 101, Folder 8)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1875", 1874-1875 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 9)
    - [Correspondence Whitmore Estate], 1875 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 10)
    - "Opinion of Chas. P. Daly; Decision Circuit Court of U.S., The NY Exhaust Ventilation Co. vs. American Institute", 1875, 1886 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 11)
    - "Petty Cash Bills, 1875" (Offsite-box 101, Folder 12)
    - Polytechnic Association of the American Institute, 1875 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 13)
    - "Reports Photographical Section 1875" (Offsite-box 102, Folder 1)
    - "Reports Board of Trustees of American Institute 1875, 1876, 1880, 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884, 1885, 1886, 1887, 1888, 1889, 1890, 1891, 1892, 1893" (1 of 2), 1875-1876, 1880-1893 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 2)
    - "Reports Board of Trustees of American Institute 1875, 1876, 1880, 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884, 1885, 1886, 1887, 1888, 1889, 1890, 1891, 1892, 1893" (2 of 2), 1875-1876, 1880-1893 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 3)
    - "New York Mutual Gas Light Co. -- Gas Bills Paid -- Exhibition Building 1875, 76, 77.", 1875-1877 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer's Acct. and Vouchers (1 of 2), 1875-1876 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 5)
    - Treasurer's Acct. and Vouchers (2 of 2), 1875-1876 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 6)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1876" (Offsite-box 102, Folder 7)
    - Amendment to Charter and Annual Report, 1876 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence -bound volumes- divided alphabetically by sender and by month 1876-1877 (1 of 3) (Offsite-box 102, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence -bound volumes- divided alphabetically by sender and by month 1876-1877 (2 of 3) (Offsite-box 103, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence -bound volumes- divided alphabetically by sender and by month 1876-1877 (3 of 3) (Offsite-box 103, Folder 2)
    - "Correspondence Whitmore Estate Excepting Letters of Mrs. Whitmore 1876", 1875-1876 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 3)
    - Legal Papers, 1876 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 4)
    - Lists and Papers - The American Institute, 1876 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 5)
    - "Reports and Papers - The American Institute - 1876" (Offsite-box 103, Folder 6)
    - "Vouchers American Institute 1876" (1 of 2), 1874-1876 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 7)
    - "Vouchers American Institute 1876" (2 of 2), 1874-1876 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 8)
    - "Petty Cash Bills 1876" (Offsite-box 103, Folder 9)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1877", 1876-1877 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 10)
    - "Annual Report of the Board of Trustees of the American Institute - Jan. 22, 1877" (Offsite-box 103, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1877 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 12)
    - "Correspondence other than with Mrs. Whitmore. 1877 For Copies of all letters written by Me since 1877, See Letter Book. C.W. Hull Trustee" (Offsite-box 103, Folder 13)
    - "Correspondence with Mrs. Whitmore 1877 For copies of letters to her since 1877- See Letter Book" (Offsite-box 103, Folder 14)
    - "Reports and Papers, American Institute, 1877", 1876-1877 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 15)
    - Reports and Papers - The American Institute, 1877-1879 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 16)
    - "Report of the Committee of the Farmers' Club on Crystallized Egg", 1877 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 1)
    - "Punchard and Gibson Paper and Nicholas Comer Papers 1877" (Offsite-box 104, Folder 2)
    - Vouchers American Institute - 1877 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 104, Folder 3)
    - Treasurer's Account and Vouchers - 1877 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 104, Folder 4)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1878", 1877-1878 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1878-1879 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 6)
    - "Annual Report of the Board of Trustees of the American Institute January 18, 1878" (Offsite-box 104, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1878-1879 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 8)
    - Legal Papers, 1878 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 9)
    - "Manuscripts Papers Read before the Farmers Club of the American Institute" (1 of 2), 1878 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 10)
    - "Manuscripts Papers Read before the Farmers Club of the American Institute" (2 of 2), 1878-1879 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 11)
    - "Reports and Papers American Institute 1878" (Offsite-box 104, Folder 12)
    - "Rough Minutes Farmer's Club May 7 to Dec. 3, 1878" (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 104, Folder 13)
    - "Rough Minutes Farmer's Club May 7 to Dec. 3, 1878" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 104, Folder 14)
    - Agreements, 1878 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 15)
    - Vouchers -- American Institute 1878 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 16)
    - Whitmore Estate Receipts (1 of 2), 1878-1883 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 1)
    - Whitmore Estate Receipts (2 of 2), 1878-1883 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 2)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1879", 1878-1879 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 3)
    - "Annual Report of the Board of Trustees of the American Institute Jan. 22nd 1879" (Offsite-box 105, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1879 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 5)
    - "Campbell vs. Ackert", 1879 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 6)
    - "Reports and Papers American Institute 1879" (Offsite-box 105, Folder 7)
    - Reports and Papers - The American Institute, 1879 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 8)
    - "Rough Minutes Farmer's Club Jan. 7 to Dec. 30, 1879" (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 105, Folder 9)
    - "Rough Minutes Farmer's Club Jan. 7 to Dec. 30, 1879" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 105, Folder 10)
    - "Expired (Old) Leases", 1879-1888 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 11)
    - Vouchers -- American Institute -- 1879 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 12)
    - Reports and Papers, N.D. [ca. 1870's] (Offsite-box 105, Folder 13)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1880" (Offsite-box 106, Folder 1)
    - "Annual Report of the Board of Trustees of the American Institute of Jan. 20, 1880" (Offsite-box 106, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (1 of 3), 1880 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (2 of 3), 1880 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (3 of 3), 1880 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 5)
    - "Reports and Papers American Institute - 1880" (Offsite-box 106, Folder 6)
    - "Rough Minutes Farmer's Club Jan. to Nov. 1880" (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 106, Folder 7)
    - "Rough Minutes Farmer's Club Jan. to Nov. 1880" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 106, Folder 8)
    - "Rough Minutes Polytechnic Section American Institute 1879, 1880, 1881", 1880-1882 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 9)
    - Agreements, 1880 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 10)
    - Vouchers American Institute 1880 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 106, Folder 11)
    - Vouchers American Institute 1880 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 107, Folder 1)
    - "Treasurer's Authority to Pay Bills 1880-1889" (Offsite-box 107, Folder 2)
    - Whitmore Estate Receipts and Papers, 1880-1881 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 3)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1881" (Offsite-box 107, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Trustees of the American Institute - January 20, 1881 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1881 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1881 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1881 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1881 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1881 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 1)
    - Rough Minutes of Farmers' Club April 5 - Dec.27, 1881 (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 108, Folder 2)
    - Rough Minutes of Farmers' Club April 5 - Dec.27, 1881 (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 108, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1881 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 4)
    - "Petty Cash Bills From March 29, 1881 to Dec. 29, 1884", 1877-1884 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 5)
    - "Vouchers American Institute 1881" (1 of 2), 1880-1882 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 6)
    - "Vouchers American Institute 1881" (2 of 2), 1880-1882 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 7)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1882" (Offsite-box 108, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - Heating and Ventilating Systems and Boilers, 1882 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence re: Photographical Section, 1882 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 2)
    - "Reports and Papers American Institute 1882", 1882, 1885 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 3)
    - "Rough Minutes -- Farmers Club -- Jan. 3 to June 2, 1882" (Offsite-box 109, Folder 4)
    - "Results of Test of Babcock G. Wilcox Brothers - Chas. W. Copeland's Report, 1882 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 5)
    - Vouchers (1 of 2), 1882-1883 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 6)
    - Vouchers (2 of 2), 1882-1883 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 7)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1883" (Offsite-box 109, Folder 8)
    - "Annual Report of the Board of Trustees of the American Institute - January 20, 1883 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 9)
    - Reports and Papers - American Institute, 1883 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 10)
    - "Rough Minutes Farmers Club 1883" (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 109, Folder 11)
    - "Rough Minutes Farmers Club 1883" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 110, Folder 1)
    - "Vouchers American Institute 1883" (1 of 2), 1882-1883 (Offsite-box 110, Folder 2)
    - "Vouchers American Institute 1883" (2 of 2), 1882-1883 (Offsite-box 110, Folder 3)
    - "Propositions for Membership 1884" (Offsite-box 110, Folder 4)
    - "Candidates for Membership 1884", 1884-1885 (Offsite-box 110, Folder 5)
    - "Annual Report of the Board of Trustees of the American Institute - January 20, 1884" (Offsite-box 110, Folder 6)
    - Farmers Club - The American Institute, 1884 (Offsite-box 110, Folder 7)
    - "Poll Lists American Institute", 1884-1899 (Offsite-box 110, Folder 8)
    - "Vouchers American Institute 1884" (1 of 2) (Offsite-box 110, Folder 9)
    - "Vouchers American Institute 1884" (2 of 2) (Offsite-box 110, Folder 10)
    - "Propositions for Membership From 1885 to 1889", 1885-1889 (Offsite-box 111, Folder 1)
    - "Annual Report of the Board of Trustees of the American Institute January 20, 1885" (Offsite-box 111, Folder 2)
    - "Reports and Papers American Institute 1885", 1882-1885 (Offsite-box 111, Folder 3)
    - Vouchers (1 of 2), 1885 (Offsite-box 111, Folder 4)
    - Vouchers (2 of 2), 1885 (Offsite-box 111, Folder 5)
    - "Petty Cash Bills I", 1885-1892 (Offsite-box 111, Folder 6)
    - "Resignations American Institute", 1886-1880, 1890-1892, 1896-1897 (Offsite-box 111, Folder 7)
    - "Annual Report of the Board of Trustees of the American Institute, January 20th, 1886.", 1884-1886 (Offsite-box 111, Folder 8)
    - Advertisements and Papers, 1886 (Offsite-box 111, Folder 9)
    - "In the Matter of the American Institute -- Opinion No. 2", 1886 (Offsite-box 111, Folder 10)
    - "Vouchers 1886" (1 of 2), 1885-1886 (Offsite-box 111, Folder 11)
    - "Vouchers 1886" (2 of 2), 1887 (Offsite-box 111, Folder 12)